Rabbi Kojo Dumgyan

UI/UX designer



- dumgyanr8@gmail.com
- 0240955003
- Accra, Ghana
- @ Portfolio
- X (Twitter)
- A Dribbble
- in LinkedIn

TOOLS & TECHNOLOGIES

Figma

UI design, prototyping

Webflow

Mobile Web designing

React

Web developement

CERTIFICATES

- Foundations of User Experience (UX) Design ∂
- Start the UX Design Process: Empathize, Define, and Ideate ℰ

INTERESTS

Coding & Designing, Researching, Reading, Football, Gaming

LANGUAGES

English

Twi

Fante

• • • • • •

PROFILE

I'm a skilled UI/UX Designer with 3+ years of experience crafting digital experiences that users love. From wireframes to prototypes, I've mastered the art of crafting intuitive interfaces that users love to click, tap, and swipe.

I sprinkle creativity and a dash of humor into every pixel. With a knack for turning complex problems into intuitive solutions, I'm on a mission to make navigating the digital world as smooth as possible.

EDUCATION

Software Engineering, Codetrain Africa *∂*

2022 - 2023 | Accra, Ghana

Participated in an intensive software training program focused on enhancing skills in UI/UX design and front-end development.

Bachelors Degree in Information Technology Management, University of Professional Studies Accra ${\mathscr S}$

2018 - 2022 | Accra, Ghana

- Developed strong analytical, problem-solving, and project management skills through coursework and projects.
- Improved technical proficiency through hands-on experience in programming fundamentals, designing and other tech related fields

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Dreamosoft, UI/UX Designer

March 2024 – present | Accra, Ghana

Collaborate with cross-functional teams to design and develop user-centered digital products.

Margins ID Group, Data entry specialist

September 2022 - December 2023

Data capturing of foreign nationals for ID card production

PROJECTS

Shuttle Hub (Still in Progress)

Currently working on a mobile shuttle app together with a team of designers and developers for university institutions in Ghana to enhance campus commuting by providing real-time tracking of the school shuttles.

SKILLS

UI/UX Design	•	•	•	•	•
User Research and testing	•	•	•	•	
Wireframing & Prototyping	•	•	•	•	•
Front-end Development (HTML/CSS/JS)	•	•	•		

COURSES

Google UX Design, Coursera